[
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "pretext": "Great job! You’ve barely scratched the surface. But still, let’s celebrate any and all progress because progress is progress, no matter how little! To celebrate, let’s go through a bunch of rapid-fire exercises. To recap our last two lessons:"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Vowels:",
    "options": ["あ – a", "い – i ", "う – u ", "え – e ", "お – o "]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "K",
    "options": ["Ka – か", "Ki – き", "Ku – く", "Ke – け", "Ko – こ"]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "S",
    "options": ["Sa - さ", "Shi - し", "Su - す", "Se - せ", "So - そ"]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Shi",
    "options": ["す", "そ", "し", "せ"],
    "answer": "し"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ka",
    "options": ["け", "そ", "か", "こ"],
    "answer": "か"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "A and E",
    "options": ["あ and い", "あ and え", "え and お", "お and あ"],
    "answer": "あ and え"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "O and U",
    "options": ["お and う", "え and い", "い and お", "お and あ"],
    "answer": "お and う"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Su",
    "options": ["し", "す", "そ", "せ"],
    "answer": "す"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ki",
    "options": ["く", "け", "か", "き"],
    "answer": "き"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ku",
    "options": ["く", "き", "け", " こ"],
    "answer": "く"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "So",
    "options": ["し", "す", "そ", "せ"],
    "answer": "そ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Se",
    "options": ["せ", "す", "さ", "そ"],
    "answer": "せ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ke",
    "options": ["き", "け", "こ", "く"],
    "answer": "け"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ko",
    "options": ["す", "き", "く", "こ"],
    "answer": "こ"
  },
  {"type": "mc", "prompt": "i", "options": ["お", "あ", "え", "い"], "answer": "い"},
  {"type": "mc", "prompt": "a", "options": ["あ", "え", "う", "お"], "answer": "あ"},
  {"type": "mc", "prompt": "e", "options": ["お", "え", "う", "い"], "answer": "え"},
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Here",
    "options": ["かお", "ここ", "いす", "すし"],
    "answer": "ここ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ai",
    "options": ["かお", "いす", "あい", "すし"],
    "answer": "あい"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Write",
    "options": ["すし", "かく", "いす", "かお"],
    "answer": "かく"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Sushi",
    "options": ["ここ", "かお", "いす", "すし"],
    "answer": "すし"
  }
]